

Kayuda Alexandr

Frontend developer



Contacts



akayuda999@gmail.com

Russia ,Rostov-on-Don

About me

I am a frontend developer with experience

SPA development using React, Redux, TypeScript, JavaScript, SCSS, HTML. In my free time I delve into familiar technologies, improve my skills, and also solve problems on Codewars, improve my knowledge of English. I will consider options for remote work, work in the office (full-time), ready for relocation.

Skills

- React/Redux
- React-Router-Dom
- Redux-Thunk
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Axios/RESTapi/Postman
- TDD/Jest/Storybook
- React-hook-form/Formik
- MaterialUI/Ant Design
- HTML5,CSS3,SCSS
- Git

Languages

- Russian(native)
- English A2 (Pre-intermediate) in progress

Work experience

My projects as frontend developer(part-time)

January 2022 - Present

CARDS

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, Axios, React-Router-dom, Material UI

TODO LIST

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Formik, MUI, Axios, React-Router-dom

SOCIAL NETWORK

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, Axios, React Hook Form, React-Router-dom

«Fresh Service»
(full time) Deputy Director

June 2019-September 2022

- · Work with clients
- Working with documents (1C trade and warehouse)
- Logistics
- · Purchase of goods

Education

2021-2022|IT-INCUBATOR Frontend developer (React/Redux/TypeScript/JS)

2011-2016|Don State Technical University
Bachelor in Automation, Mechatronics and Control, Automation
of Technological Processes and Production (by industry)